https://recording-history.org/privacy-policy/

your password
Forgot your password?
Privacy Policy
Who we areOur website address is: https://recording-history.org.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsWho we share your data withHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Your contact informationAdditional informationHow we protect your dataWhat data breach procedures we have in placeWhat third parties we receive data fromWhat automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataIndustry regulatory disclosure requirements
Rock Music
Top 10 Motörhead Songs
Matthew -
November 20, 2020
Often regarded as the heroes who revived the heavy metal scene in the late 70s and early 80s, British rock band Motörhead have produced...
Rock Music
Top 10 Grateful Dead Songs
Matthew -
September 16, 2020
Formed around 65’ Grateful Dead is one of the most influential bands of the time. They were significantly popular and one of the most...
Music
Top 10 Songs About Friendship
Matthew -
September 16, 2020
When partying with your friends or just hanging out with them, one thing that we all do is play some tunes be it for...
Rock Music
Top 10 Fall Out Boy Love Songs
Matthew -
September 16, 2020
From their beginnings as an angsty emotional four-piece from Illinois at the turn of the thousand years, Fall Out Boy have discharged six studio...
Pop
Top 10 One Direction Songs
Matthew -
September 16, 2020
After competing on Season 7 of The X Factor (UK) in 2010, the English-Irish boy band One Direction became international popstars.
With their magazine appearance...
ABOUT USWe provide you with the latest breaking songs, artists straight from the entertainment industry.
Recording-history.org is a participant in the Amazon.com Services LLC Associates Program. As an Amazon Associate we earn from qualifying purchases. Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.
About us
Contact us
Privacy Policy
© Copyright 2019 - Recording-History.org
